我是罗素  请留言
This is Russo. Please leave a message.
他不接我电话
He's not answering my calls.
都结束了  他肯定明白
It's over, and he must know it.
你认为他不可能卷土重来了
You don't think there's any way he can recover?
共和党会在每个电台和电视台
The Republicans will play that interview
反复播放那段采访
on every radio and television station
从现在直到11月5日
from now until November 5th.
美国大选为11月第一个星期二  2012年大选是11月6号
我同情那个孩子
I sympathize with the kid,
但我从一开始就担心这个
but this was my concern from the beginning.
我该听你的  先生
And I should've listened to you, sir.
我以为他能顶住压力
I thought he could handle the pressure.
好吧  他退出了
Okay. So he withdraws.
我们要找人代替他
We need to replace him.
你有人选吗
You have any ideas?
只剩不到两个月
With less than two months to go?
如果总统让我参与之前的讨论
If the President hadn't shut me out of the early discussions,
我没准能提出些好人选
I could've come up with some good options,
但我想不出有谁
but I don't know anyone
同时拥有知名度和金主捐款
who's got the name recognition and donor base
能够在七周内从零开始发起竞选
to start a campaign from scratch just seven weeks out.
让我想想
Let me think.
接下来的几分钟将决定一切
Everything hinges on the next few minutes...
我数月来的谋划  我走的每一步
all my months of planning, every move I've made.
-有一个人选  -谁
- There is one person. - Who?
你  副总统先生
You, Mr. Vice President.
如果你重新竞选州长
If you ran to reclaim your seat,
一定能获得压倒性胜利
I think you'd win by a landslide.
辞去副总统职务
Resign the vice presidency.
赢了的话
Only if you win.
沃克2016年的大选需要我
Walker needs me for 2016.
你敢打包票他还会留着你吗
Are you entirely certain he's gonna keep you on the ticket?
你们二人的不和已不是秘密
I mean, it's no secret the two of you don't exactly get along.
他说什么了
What has he said?
你这不是让我难办吗  副总统先生
Oh, you're putting me in a very awkward position, Mr. Vice President.
他有说我坏话吗
Has he been bad-mouthing me?
他的原话是
Well, the exact phrase he used was
"讨厌鬼"
"Pain in the ass."
那个混蛋
That fucker.
他缺乏领导力
He's got no idea how to lead,
不懂尊重
no sense of respect.
-是他的主意吗  -不
- Oh, is this his idea? - No.
-他想借机摆脱我  -不  是我昨天想到的
- His way of getting rid of me? - No. It struck me yesterday,
我觉得值得商榷
and I just thought it was worth suggesting.
但我还没和其他人讨论过
But, no, I haven't discussed this with anyone.
那就好
And you shouldn't.
没有人会傻到离开白宫去当州长
People don't leave the White House to become a governor.
我能问你个私人问题吗  先生
May I ask you a personal question, sir?
你真的想做副总统吗
Do you want to be the Vice President?
彼得说  你在帮他竞选拉票时
Peter said that when you were out on that campaign trail,
充满激情与活力
you had so much enthusiasm and energy
他以为你也许怀念做州长的日子
that he thought you maybe missed being the Governor.
的确
I do miss it.
那为什么不回去呢
Then why not go back?
你会成为这次竞选的英雄
You could be the hero of this election
在2016年大选中保住民主党在宾州的胜利
and secure Pennsylvania for the Democrats in 2016.
加勒特不可能同意的
Garrett would never go along with something like this,
就算他恨我入骨
even if he hates my guts.
这会让他显得无力
It would make him look weak,
好像他控制不住自己的政府
like he's lost control of the administration.
如果这是双方的决定呢
Not if it was a mutual decision.
让我去找加勒特
Look, let me talk to Garrett.
我不会提及我们今天的谈话
I won't mention that we've spoken.
知道他怎么想也算有益无害
I suppose there's no harm in finding out what he thinks.
谢谢  副总统先生
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
-四百分口号  -1976年  他再次让我们骄傲
- Slogans for 400. - "1976. He's making us proud again."
-D.J.  -卡特
- D.J. - Who is Carter.
-错  约翰  -福特
- No. John. - Who is Ford.
彼得
Peter?
六百分口号
Slogans for 600.
彼得  在吗
Peter, are you here?
1888年  爷爷的帽子很适合本
"1888. Grandfather's hat fits Ben."
-克劳迪娅  -本杰明・哈里森
- Claudia. - Who is Benjamin Harrison.
-正确  -八百分总统竞选口号
- Yes. - Presidential slogans for 800.
1990年  晚餐吃得饱
"1900. The full dinner pail "
在火车上
On the train ride down,
我差点就要叫警察闯进来
I almost called the police to have them break in
看看你有没有伤害自己
and make sure you hadn't hurt yourself.
我不想问你发生了什么
I'm not gonna even ask you what happened.
现在无关紧要了
It doesn't matter right now.
1964年  "你心里知道他是对的"
现在要紧的是...
What matters right now...
-要紧的...  -戈德华特
- What matters... - Who is Goldwater.
-克劳迪娅  -戈德华特
- Claudia - Who is Goldwater.
巴里・戈德华特  正确
Barry Goldwater. Yes.
拜托  我正在看呢
Oh, come on. Hey, I'm watching that.
要紧的是公寓外面的50个记者
What matters is the 50 reporters in front of your building
还有150名竞选工作人员
and the 150 campaign staffers
还不知道自己是否已经失业
who don't know if they still have a job.
都结束了
It's over.
我知道
I know.
让他们都走吧
So, tell them to go away.
怎么  你打算就这么窝在这儿
What, are you just gonna hole yourself up in here
希望一切都消失吗
and hope it all goes away?
差不多就是这样了
Yeah, that's pretty much the plan.
我不能让你这样
Well, I won't let you.
放下
Hey, put that down. Hey.
-给我放下  -彼得
- Hey, put that down! - Peter...
我们得发表个声明
We need to put out a statement.
准备好了打电话给我
Call me when you're prepared to do that.
我会在费城的总部
I'll be at the headquarters in Philly.
我怕我对你的感情变得太深
I was scared that I was starting to feel too much for you.
所以我才做了了断
I think that's why I ended it.
你不允许自己害怕吗
And you have no room for fear?
不  害怕成不了事
No. Being afraid doesn't accomplish anything.
不对  我在海外时
That's not true. When I'm overseas,
合理的恐惧  像对疾病  暴力
rational fear... disease or violence...
这种恐惧让你生存下去
that sort of fear keeps you alive.
回到这儿  老天
Back here, God,
我感觉自己害怕些
I find myself afraid of things
虚无缥缈的东西
that I can't name or point to.
就比如  我有多渺小
It's like, uh, how little am I seeing?
或者我是不是浪费了此时此日
Or have I wasted this day or this moment?
是啊  我有时也会想
Yeah, I think that sometimes...
我的人生到底有没有意义
whether my life will add up.
弗兰西斯听到我说这些
Francis would roll his eyes
一定会翻白眼
if he heard me talking like this.
他知道你在哪吗
Does he know where you are?
不知道
No, he doesn't.
如果他在找你  你就在那儿
If he's looking for you, that's where you are.
那里
Over there.
你遇见弗兰克之前
Before you met Frank.
独自一人
Alone.
充满好奇
Curious.
接纳一切事物
Absorbing everything.
你才不知道我年轻时是什么样的
You have no idea what I was like when I was a girl.
他知道你的那一面吗
Did he ever know that side of you?
他对那女孩不感兴趣
He wasn't interested in that girl.
我也是
And neither was I.
那你对什么感兴趣
What were you interested in?
不仅是观察别人
Being more than an observer.
你想受人瞩目
You wanted to be seen.
不只是受到瞩目
Not just seen.
我要举足轻重
I wanted to be significant.
历史上没有先例
There's no historical precedent.
阿伦・伯尔就曾竞选过州长
Aaron Burr ran for Governor,
卡尔霍恩也曾竞选过参议员
Calhoun for the Senate.
那都是两百年前的事了
200 years ago.
一个曾在决斗中杀人  另一个支持奴隶制
One shot a man in a duel, the other believed in slavery.
阿伦・伯尔在决斗中杀死了亚历山大・哈密尔顿
卡尔霍恩主张奴隶制度是完美的制度
我们真要跟这种人相比吗  弗兰克
Is that really the sort of company we wanna share, Frank?
总统先生  我们可能要
Mr. President, we stand losing
失去一个重要的摇摆州
control of an important swing state,
和议会多数党席位
our majority in the house,
甚至是您的连任
and quite possibly your second term in office.
要扭转局势就得采取非常手段
Preventing all of that may require unconventional measures.
别人会以为是我容不下他
It would look like I'm pushing him out.
或者更糟  以为他是抛弃了我们
Or worse... that he's abandoning the administration.
你们可以发布一份联合声明
You make a joint statement.
就说  除非竞选获胜  否则他不会辞职
You say he won't resign unless he wins.
而如果他输掉选举  就继续任副总统
If he loses, he stays on as Vice President.
这样就没人会指责你们背叛彼此了
No one could accuse either of you of disloyalty to the other.
这是吉姆的主意吗
Did Jim come to you with this?
不  这完全是我的想法
No. It's entirely my idea.
在得到您的首肯之前
I wouldn't dream of speaking to
我绝不会向副总统提及此事
the Vice President without passing it by you first.
我想他会很受冒犯
I think he'd take it as an affront,
好像我想摆脱他似的
like I'm trying to get rid of him.
老实说  先生  我倒觉得
Honestly, sir, I think
他对这事会比您想的感兴趣得多
he might be more interested than you imagine.
-为什么  -我本来不想提的
- Why is that? - Well, I hesitate to bring this up,
但在帮罗素宣传期间
but when he was campaigning for Russo,
他曾对您颇有微词  先生
he spoke quite freely about you, sir.
说说看
Tell me.
当然  我是听彼得转述的
Of course, I'm getting this secondhand from Peter,
但大概是说
but the gist of it is that...
说您完全没有领导力
that you lack entirely in leadership,
还不懂得尊重人
and that you have no sense of respect.
他还想承担更多责任呢
And he wants more responsibility.
这么口无遮拦  毫无自律
And how do I give him that when he shows
我怎么能给他重任呢
absolutely no discretion, no discipline?
这正是我想说的
Well, that is entirely my point. Now, look,
我为支持罗素竞选的事负全责
I take full responsibility for backing Russo,
但塞翁失马焉知非福
but there could be a silver lining in all this.
也许您能一箭双雕
You could accomplish two goals:
为民主党保住宾州
Secure Pennsylvania for the Democrats
又能名正言顺地换掉马修斯
and find an honorable way to replace Matthews.
你怎么看
What do you think?
我觉得事关重大
I think it is a very big decision,
最好三思而后行
and we do not want to make it impulsively.
我同意  我要再考虑考虑
I agree. I'd like to put some more thought into it.
这很谨慎  先生  不过别忘了
Well, that is very prudent, sir. Just bear in mind,
还有七周时间  我们得分秒必争
seven weeks out, that every day counts.
-你好  先生  -多少钱
- Hi, sir. - How much is it?
发票在我这儿
Oh, I got your receipt right here.
不不不  只要40美金
No, no, no. It was... it was just $40.
拿着吧  别告诉别人  行吗
Yeah. Don't tell anyone, all right?
我不会泄露住户的隐私
No. I... I never say anything about our tenants.
-记者还守在外面吗  -是的
- The press still outside? - Yeah.
我照你的吩咐  告诉他们你不在
I told them you weren't here, like you said.
多数都走了  但有几个还在外面
Most of them left. There's still, you know, a few, though.
有没有能让我
If I wanted to leave,
不声不响离开这儿的路
is there a place I could do it without being seen?
有  可以坐货梯直达车库
Yeah. The freight elevator down to the garage.
我可以叫辆出租车或是
I could call you a cab or...
好吧  谢谢  再说吧
All right. Thanks. I'll let you know.
罗素先生
Mr. Russo, uh...
算我多管闲事吧  不过
sir, it's none of my business,but, uh,
我叔叔也曾经酒瘾复发过
my uncle... he fell off the wagon a few times.
那时候最好的解决办法就是找个人陪着
When he did, the best thing for him was just not to be alone.
我把钱还你  把酒拿走
I'll give you this money back, I'll take that bag off your hands,
进去陪陪你
come in here, keep you company...
谢谢你  如果我改变主意会叫你的
I appreciate it. I'll let you know if I change my mind.
弗兰西斯・安德伍德  能过来一趟吗  我们得谈谈
坐吧
Sit down.
克莱尔在哪
Where's Claire?
不在这儿
Not here.
这是什么意思  除后患吗
So what is this, tying up loose ends?
我可不敢
I wouldn't presume.
你这样的人怎么可能除干净呢
People like you can't be neatly tied up.
我想或许我们可以...
But I thought perhaps we could start...
真有品味
It's very tasteful.
这是她庆典上穿的那件礼服
This is the dress she wore to the gala.
我想是的
I believe so.
就是的
It is.
我记得这件
I recognize it.
回卧室去
Go back into the bedroom.
这焦距对得真不错
I'm amazed how well you got her in focus.
叫她什么好呢
What should we call her?
她为什么一定要有名字
Why does she need a name?
我拍照一定要知道对方的名字
I never photograph anyone without knowing their name.
不是你拍的  我拍的
You didn't take the photograph. I did.
我觉得该叫她克莱尔
I think we should call her Claire.
她长得一点都不像我
She doesn't even look like me.
跟我年轻时也不像  你怎么老这么说啊
Not even a younger version. Why do you keep saying that?
不是指她的五官  而是表情
Not her features, her expression.
我们应该裱起来  你可以挂在家里
Hey, we should mount it. You can hang her in your house.
弗兰西斯会反对吗
Would Francis object?
我们能不能别提弗兰西斯
Can we please not discuss Francis?
是你在公园里先提起他的
You brought him up in the park.
我知道  我的错
I know I did, and I shouldn't have.
那我们得假装他不存在吗
So we have to pretend he doesn't exist?
我以为我们可以无话不谈
I thought we could talk about anything.
他其实就在这儿  你得承认这点
He is a presence here. You must admit that.
昨天你一进门
When you walked through the door yesterday,
他就和你一起来了
he walked right in with you.
只是我一个人  没有别人
It's just me, nobody else.
你就自欺欺人吧  说不定会成真
You keep telling yourself that, it might come true.
你觉得她要是知道我穿她的礼服  会怎么想
How do you think she'd feel if she knew I was wearing this?
我说不准
I don't know.
你不认为她会不高兴吗
You don't think she'd be upset?
她也许会说你穿起来很好看
She'd probably say you look very beautiful in it.
像钢一样
It's like steel.
你应该放回去
You should put it back.
我要了
I think I'll keep it.
如果你愿意的话  我可以为你买件一样
I'll buy you one of your own, if you'd like.
不用  我就要这件
No. I want this one.
她去过我卧室
She came into my bedroom.
她该知道我也来过她卧室
She should know I came into hers.
你们的床总是铺得这么整齐吗
Is your bed always so perfectly made?
这是我在军校养成的习惯
It's a habit I formed at military school.
她睡哪边
What side of the bed does she sleep on?
那边
That side.
让她留着吧
She can keep it.
反正也更适合她
Fits her better anyway.
听着  佐伊
Listen, Zoe...
不论是刚才楼上的事
Whatever just happened upstairs,
还是这过去的六个月的事
whatever these past six months have been,
现在是不是该简化这段关系了呢
can we agree that it is time to simplify?
怎么个简化法
What does simple look like?
像你之前说的那样  维持公事往来
We maintain our professional arrangement, as you suggested,
我会尊重你的决定
which I will honor.
你还信任我吗
You still trust me?
我还能怎么办
What choice do I have?
你没像你说的那样伤害我或者遗弃我
You didn't hurt me or discard me like you said you would.
我很庆幸没这必要
I'm glad I didn't have to.
那好  我们可以简化
Yes, we'll agree to simplify.
很好
Good.
抱歉我迟了几分钟  弗兰克
Sorry I'm a few minutes late, Frank.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
我想我很清楚你要见我的原因
I have a pretty good idea why you asked for this meeting.
-你和总统谈过了吗  -谈过了
- Have you and the President had a chance to speak? - We have.
-他什么意见  -他很纠结
- Is he leaning one way or another? - He's torn.
-你呢  -我没那么纠结
- And what about you? - I'm a little less torn.
直觉告诉我这是个错误
My instincts tell me it's a mistake.
你想要说服我吗
You wanna convince me otherwise?
听着  如果直觉告诉你
Well, look, if your instincts tell you
不应该这么做  我不打算...
this is not the way to go, I'm not about to...
弗兰克  我要问你两个很直白的问题
Frank, I'm gonna ask you two very direct questions,
希望你能直白地回答
and I would appreciate direct answers.
你把我儿子弄进大学时
When you got my son into college,
是不是就指着有这么一天
were you anticipating a moment like this?
什么意思
I don't follow.
真的吗  弗兰克
Honestly, Frank?
我指...
Was I antici...
我要是知道你想问什么
I would be happy to answer you directly
我一定直白地回答你
if I knew what you were asking.
好吧  我问第二个问题
All right. I will ask you my second question.
你是不是自己想当副总统
Do you want the Vice Presidency for yourself?
如果总统愿意委任于我  那是他...
I would serve at the pleasure of the President. That was his...
你提出这个建议就是为取代马修斯
You proposed this idea so that you can take Matthews' place.
-我可没说过  -但这是你想要的
- I did not say that. - But it is what you want.
-我想要...  -总统任命你为副总统
- What I want is in the... - The President makes you V.P.,
2016年你继续连任
he keeps you on the ticket in 2016,
再把这当成2020年竞选总统的跳板
and you use that as a springboard to run in 2020.
告诉我你从未想过这些
Tell me that trajectory has never entered your mind.
琳达  我习惯
Well, Linda, I make a habit of
考虑任何情况下可能发生的事
considering all trajectories in any given situation.
但这是为大局  不是为了我自己
But that's a practical exercise, not a personal one.
那你是不承认吗
So you refuse to admit it.
承认我是否想要这结果  这毫不相干
Admit it's what I want? That's irrelevant.
是你安排了这次会面  不是我
You're the one who asked for this meeting, not me.
这次会面是想要解决问题
This meeting's about trying to solve a problem,
不是满足个人野心
not fulfill some personal ambition.
但如果两者可兼得  你不会反对
But if both could be achieved, you wouldn't object.
不管总统想要谁
I think this is a sound course of action
接替马修斯  这么做都合情合理
regardless of who the President taps to replace Matthews.
现在我得赌上一切了
I must gamble everything I have right now.
如果我说实话  可能会落人口实
If I'm honest, she may use it against me.
如果不说  她又不会帮我
If I'm not, she won't lift a finger.
我自己也用过这策略
I've used the same tactic myself.
一个人的目的一旦暴露
Once someone is exposed,
他们就得听你发落
they're at your mercy.
她想要我亲口说出来
She wants to hear me say the words.
没错
Yes.
我想当副总统
I want to be the Vice President.
没错  我把你儿子弄进大学
And, yes, I helped your son get into college
是希望你能还我一个人情
in the hopes that you would return the favor.
但我不能逼你这么做  琳达
But I can't force you to do so, Linda.
我还觉得我们应该强强联手
But I also think that we would make a formidable team.
即使存在分歧
Look what we've been able to accomplish
我们都能做成这么多大事
even when we've been at odds with each other.
如果我们达成一致  那又会是怎样的局面
Now put your mind to what we could accomplish if we weren't.
感谢你的宝贵时间  琳达
Thank you for taking the time, Linda.
我再打给你  怎么样了
I'll call you back. How'd it go?
她深藏不露啊
She's holding her cards very close to the chest.
-有彼得的消息吗  -没有
- Any word from Peter? - Nothing.
克里斯蒂娜说他不肯离开公寓
Christina said he wouldn't leave the apartment.
但我打给门卫  他说彼得走了
But I called the doorman, and he said that Peter was gone.
-去哪了  -他不知道
- Where? - He doesn't know.
他得正式退选给沃克施加压力
He needs to officially withdraw to put pressure on Walker.
我正在找他
I'm trying to track him down.
你为什么一开始不看好他
Why'd you let him out of your sight in the first place?
我以为他在洗澡
I thought he was showering.
我和你打电话时他跑掉了
He disappeared when I was on the phone with you.
计划是这样的  道格
There was a plan here, Doug.
他搞砸了  然后退选
He explodes, he withdraws,
我们帮他振作起来  再让他悄悄离开
we put him back together, and he quietly goes away.
罗素自昨天早上
Russo has made no public appearances
被人认为醉酒后接受匹兹堡
since allegations that he was inebriated
WZPZ电台采访至今仍未公开露面
during a radio interview on WZPZ Pittsburgh yesterday morning.
据民主党领导人透露
Sources among the Democratic leadership have suggested
党派正在考虑由谁来取代罗素
that the party is currently considering options to replace Russo.
同时  据昨晚CNN登记选民民调显示
Meanwhile, Republican candidate Jack Swofford's lead
共和党候选人杰克・斯沃夫
has jumped to a 24-point margin,
支持率猛增  已领先24个百分点
according to an overnight CNN poll of registered voters.
斯沃夫竞选团队的
The Swofford campaign
资助金额也急剧攀升
is also reporting a sharp spike in contributions...
过去20小时内筹集了近五十万美金
nearly half a million dollars in the last 20...
罗素尚未露面  竞选堪忧
我今早看见了
I saw that this morning.
是弗兰西斯让彼得竞选的
Francis got Peter to run.
你认识他吗
Do you know him well?
不太熟
We weren't close.
你需要打电话吗
Do you need to make calls?
-我可以去别的房间  -不用
- 'Cause I can head into the other room. - I don't think so.
谢了
Thanks.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
去暗室  我今天应该去的
To the lab. I should've gone in today.
亚当
Adam.
-亚当  -你走  快走
- Adam... - Just go. Go. Leave.
你觉得我们还能维持多久
How long do you think this can possibly go on for?
我们在一起的时间从没超过两天
We have never spent more than 48 hours together.
或许是有原因的
Maybe there's a reason for that.
我心里仍有一部分爱着你
A part of me still loves you.
哪一部分
Which part?
我不能做一个休息站  克莱尔
I can't be just a pit stop, Claire,
-或是避风港  -拜托
- or some sort of escape... - Oh, come on.
-你不止如此  -或是填补
- You're more than that. - ... or a top-up on
-弗兰西斯不能给你的一切  -少来
- whatever Francis can't provide. - Oh, fuck off!
他是我丈夫  亚当
He's my husband, Adam.
我们经历的事远超出你的想象
We've gone through more than you could ever imagine.
我嫉妒并被你的自由自所吸引
I envy your free spirit, and I'm attracted to it,
并不是所有人都有这福分
but not all of us have that luxury.
这也是你让我失望的地方  克莱尔
Which is what I find so frustrating about you, Claire.
你可以选择的
You... you had a choice.
但你选择放弃自由
You chose not to be free.
不  我选了个能爱他超过一周的男人
No. What I chose was a man I could love for more than a week.
我不该那么说
I shouldn't have said that. I...
至少你说了实话
At least you're being honest.
我无法像你这样活在当下  亚当
I can't live moment to moment like you, Adam.
我和弗兰西斯有过去  有未来
I have a history with Francis, I have a future with him,
那比一时要大
and it's bigger than a moment.
那你应该扼杀
Then you should kill it...
你仍爱着我的那部分
whatever part of you still loves me.
如果你办不到
If you can't,
我会的
I will.
-亚当  -不
- Adam... - No.
-喂  -亲爱的
- Hello? - Hey. Hey, sweetie.
你怎么样  我  你妈在旁边吗
How's it going? I'm... are you with your mom?
她在楼下  要我叫她来接吗
She's downstairs. You want me to go get her?
不  我只想打过来
No. No. I just wanted to call and say,
跟你和你弟弟打个招呼
you know, hey to your... uh, your brother and you.
他在吗
Is he... is he there?
他大概在自己房里
He's in his room, I think.
好吧  你能去叫他吗
Okay. You wanna go get him?
等等
Hold on.
他说不想和你说话
He says he doesn't want to talk to you.
什么
What?
为什么
Why not?
我们看新闻了  爸爸
We've seen the news, dad.
昨天好多媒体都跑来我们学校
There were all sorts of TV cameras at our school yesterday.
妈妈让我们这周待在家里
Mom's making us stay home this week.
我想让你做件事  我想让你
I want you to do something. I want you to go to, uh,
到卧室窗边  往外看
your bedroom window and look out.
看见那辆黑车了吗
You see that black car?
-嗯  -我在里面
- Yeah. - That's me.
你不该在这儿的  爸爸  妈妈会发火的
You shouldn't be here, dad. Mom would be really angry.
我们不跟她说  好吗
Well, we don't need to tell her. Right?
就当作...
It'll just be... it'll just be, uh...
我们之间的小秘密
it'll just be our little secret.
你的声音很奇怪
Your voice sounds weird,
就像在广播里那样
like it did on the radio.
你听了那个
You... you heard that?
我有电脑
I have a computer.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我...有时候爸爸也会犯错
I...sometimes your dad makes mistakes.
-我要挂了  -别
- I better go. - No.
我不想听到你这样的声音
I don't like to hear your voice when it's like this.
让我难过  再见  爸爸
It makes me sad. Bye, dad.
萨拉  别...
Sarah, please...
克里斯蒂娜
彼得
Peter?
克里斯蒂娜
Christina.
你在哪里
Where are you?
我...
I'm, uh...
我现在...感觉不怎么好
I'm not... I'm not... I'm not doing so well.
你在哪里  彼得
Where are you, Peter?
-在车里  -你在开车吗
- I'm in my car. - Are you driving?
没有
No.
告诉我你在哪里
Tell me where you are.
在我孩子家门外
I'm outside my kids' house.
-你是说玛德琳的家  -对
- You mean Madeleine's? - Yeah.
我要你待在那儿别动
I need you to stay right there.
好吗  彼得
Okay, Peter?
你能待在那儿吗
You'll stay there?
彼得
Peter.
彼得  还在听吗
Peter, are you still there?
喂
Hello?
警察局
我要自首
I'd like to turn myself in.
什么事
For what?
几个月前
A few months ago,
我因醉驾被警察拦下
I was pulled over for drunk driving.
他们放我走了  我应该被定罪的
They let me go. I should've been convicted.
如果你当时被释放了  先生
Well, if you were let go, sir,
我们现在不能逮捕你
we can't arrest you for it now.
我醉驾开过来的  为这个逮捕我吧
Well, I drunk drove here. Arrest me for that.
我们可以送你去戒酒间...
We can put you in a detox tank...
我想被正式拘捕
I wanna be formally arrested.
我是彼得・罗素议员
My name is Congressman Peter Russo.
一月曾在密歇根大道被捕
I was arrested in January on Michigan Avenue.
请稍坐一下  议员先生
Please have a seat, Congressman.
我去打几个电话
I gotta make a few phone calls.
你找到他了吗
Have you found him?
我在他前妻家外面
I'm in front of his ex-wife's house.
克里斯蒂娜说他在这儿打了电话
Christina said he called from there.
-他不在那儿  -是的
- He's not there? - No.
但手机在  扔在了路边
But his phone is. I found it by the curb.
那么我们就联系不上他了
So we have no way to contact him?
除非他主动联系我们
Not unless he reaches out to us.
这不太妙
This isn't good.
要我去报案吗
Want me to alert the authorities?
我们再给他点时间
Let's give him a little longer.
-你们交往了多久  -大概半年
- How long did it last? - About six months.
-他比我大  -大很多吗
- He was older. - A lot?
对
Yeah.
是个记者  还是在国会工作
Was he a journalist, or did he work on The Hill?
这我还是不说了
I'd rather not say.
好吧
All right.
我之前有段时间很尊敬他
He was someone I looked up to... for a while.
为什么结束
Why did it end?
他有妻子
He has a wife.
我们都知道最终会结束的
We both knew it was gonna end eventually.
我是说  真是...
I mean, it was really...
糟糕透顶
it was fucked up.
我们在一起的第一晚
The first night we spent together,
他说  他会伤害我  然后遗弃我
he told me he was gonna hurt me and then discard me.
结束的时候  我对他说  他都没做到
And when it ended, I told him that he'd done neither.
但...
But...
我确实很受伤
it does hurt.
我不会伤害你
I won't hurt you.
这你不能保证
Yeah, you can't promise me that.
我能
Yes, I can.
-有人见过他吗  -没有
- Has anyone else seen him? - No.
他独自一人待在审讯室里
He's in an interrogation room by himself.
我就不该搅这趟浑水
I never should've got mixed up with this fucking mess.
现在后悔太迟了  巴尼
We're way behind regret time, Barney.
别让人看见他
Just have your guys keep him out of sight.
给我找个后门
I'll need a back exit.
-我来吧  谢谢  -好
- I got him. Thanks. - Yeah.
走吧
Come on.
彼得
Hey, Peter.
你的车在哪里
Where's your car?
街那头
It's down the street.
我送你回家吧
I'll drive you home.
你去我家  让密查姆给你开门
You go back to mine, have Meechum let you in.
-这边吗  -嗯
- This way? - Yeah.
你在想什么啊  彼得
What were you thinking, Peter?
我得为我的行为负责
I need to take responsibility for my actions.
让自己蹲监狱吗
By getting yourself thrown in jail?
真正地负责
Real responsibility.
就像互戒会聚会时说的那样
Like... like they talk about in the meetings,
而不是为竞选而撒的谎
not the lies we told for the campaign.
你刚才的行为太鲁莽了
What you just did was extremely reckless.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我明天要做一份声明  弗兰克
I'm making a statement tomorrow, Frank.
关于退出竞选吗
About pulling out of the race?
那不够  我...
That's not enough. I...
我不能再逃避了
I need to stop hiding.
那我们一起研究措辞
Well, let's work together on the language.
我得独立完成  必须是我自己的话
I have to do it on my own. It's gotta be my own words.
听着  彼得  这不单是你的事了  好吗
Look, Peter, this isn't just about you anymore, all right?
-让我帮你  -我不要你帮忙
- Let me help you. - I don't want your help.
我被捕的时候也没求过你帮忙
I didn't never ask your help when you... I got arrested.
你的帮助对我有什么好处
When did your help ever help me?
你怎么生活我不管
You can live your life the way you want to.
但也别来管我怎么过
I'm done being told how to live mine.
肯定有办法  既能担起责任
Well, there has to be a way to take responsibility without
又不用毁了一切
shattering everything.
你至少愿意跟我探讨下这个吗
Are you at least willing to have that discussion?
-要我上楼吗  -不用了
- Do you want me to come upstairs? - No.
我知道你很痛苦  彼得
I know you're in a lot of pain, Peter.
但今晚我不想你觉得痛苦
But I don't want you to feel any pain tonight.
给  从明天开始改头换面吧
Here. You can start fresh tomorrow.
喝吧  我不会说什么  我也来点
Go ahead. I won't judge you. Hell, I'll even join you.
放松
Just relax.
你到家了
You're home now.
不管你明天要面对什么
Whatever it is you have to face tomorrow,
现在都不用去想
you don't have to face it now.
这儿只有你和我
Right now it's just you and me.
其他的都无关紧要
The rest of the world doesn't matter.
你的孩子  克里斯蒂娜
Your children, Christina...
他们会原谅你的
they will forgive you,
因为他们爱你  彼得
because you're loved, Peter.
辜负
Failed.
我辜负了自己
I failed myself.
我的家庭
I failed my family.
还有竞选
I failed the campaign.
别这么说  彼得
No, you haven't, Peter.
我能来点吗
May I?
我跟克莱尔刚结婚时
You know, when Claire and I were first married,
也谈过要孩子的事
we talked about having children.
我直接说我不想要孩子
I told her flat out I didn't want any.
这很自私  却很诚实
It was selfish but honest.
我的童年并不幸福
I didn't have a particularly happy childhood.
我猜你也一样
I suspect you didn't either.
是的
No.
谁都避不开痛苦
You see, no person avoids pain.
既然是如此  我觉得就不该要孩子
And I just didn't think it was right to bring a child in knowing that.
但当我回想过去
But now when I think back, I...
才意识到这很懦弱
I realize that was cowardly.
当我看到你
I see you,
我就想  这人很勇敢
and I think, well, there's a brave man,
比我勇敢得多
far braver than me.
我好累
I'm so tired.
当我想到
When I... when I think about... when I...
我好累
I'm so tired.
闭上眼睛吧
You should close your eyes.
忘掉一切
Let it all go.
我们有的是时间
We have all the time in the world.
彼得
Peter?
Peter.
我走回来的
I walked back.
不管接下来几小时发生了什么
Whatever happens in the next few hours,
无论你听到什么
whatever you hear,
我们都永远不提
we will never speak of it.
先生
Sir...
半小时前琳达打来电话
I heard from Linda about a half an hour ago.
总统想见你
The President wants to meet with you.
八点半
8:30.
什么事
About what?
不清楚
I don't know.
弗兰克
Frank.
你最初提出这主意时  我并不赞同
Now, when you brought up this idea, I wasn't sold.
我觉得这主意太极端  欠考虑
It struck me as both desperate and careless.
但琳达列出了所有好处
But then Linda laid out all the pros,
显然是好处多于坏处
and they clearly outweigh the cons.
我把道理解释给吉姆听
I explained our reasoning to Jim
希望他不会以为我疯了
and hoped he wouldn't think I was off my rocker.
最初很难接受
I did at first,
但总统说了些很有力的理由
but the President made some very good arguments.
这一招很大胆  弗兰克
It's a bold move, Frank.
我很佩服
I'm very impressed.
感谢你愿意考虑  先生
Well, thank you, sir, for being open to the idea.
谢谢您敢于承担风险  总统先生
And thank you, Mr. President, for taking the risk.
这要一步步来
We'll need to work this out step by step.
执行过程不能有一丝差错
The execution has to be perfect.
罗素那边怎么样了  有他的消息吗
Where are things with Russo? Any word from him yet?
我们还在找他
We're still trying to locate him.
-需要担心他吗  -他失踪两天了
- Well, is there any cause for worry? - It's been two days.
不得不承认  我有点担心
I am a bit worried, I have to admit.
他现在肯定很难熬
I mean, this must be an extremely difficult moment for him.
希望他会尽快联系我们
We're hoping he'll reach out shortly.
派我们的人调查  我想知道他在哪
Let's get our people on it. I wanna know where he is.
一旦他退出竞选  我们得迅速行动
Now, once he withdraws, we have to move quickly.
我们会像你说的  发布联合声明
We'll make a joint statement, as you proposed.
我认为意思很明确
It's a clear message, I think.
宾州人对我们很重要
Pennsylvanians matter to us,
我们不能让他们失望
and we're not gonna let them down.
没错
That's right.
我会说吉姆对白宫的价值无法估量
I'll say that Jim's an invaluable asset to the White House,
但我很敬佩他为他的家乡人民
but that I have great admiration for the sacrifice
所甘愿作出的牺牲
he's willing to make for the people of his home state.
除非他当选  否则您绝不允许他辞职
And you should not accept his resignation until he's elected.
这显得您依然信任他
That will show your continuing commitment to him.
这主意很好
I think that's a good idea.
只要我能全身心投入竞选  我就同意
As long as I can devote myself wholly to the campaign, I agree.
如果吉姆当选
Now, should Jim win,
我们就得立即提名一位副总统
we'll need to nominate a Vice President immediately.
琳达  你开始拟名单了吗
Linda, you're putting together a list of names?
是的  缩小选择范围以后
Yes. And you can begin the vetting process
就可以开始审查了
as soon as you narrow down the choices.
我已经拟了一份主要竞争者的名单
I already have a short list of top contenders.
吉姆  我希望你也提出意见
I want your input on that, Jim.
乐意至极
More than happy.
议员先生
Congressman?
我们可以利用现有的人员部署
We can use the existing infrastructure.
你愿跟纳什・埃伦斯合作吗
Are you okay with Nash Aarons?
我喜欢纳什  但我想找点我自己的人
I like Nash, but I'll want to bring in some of my own people.
没问题的  纳什擅长团队协作
Well, that won't be a problem. Nash is a team player.
我们可以重新安排你部分
And we can reallocate some of your
-2016年再选资金  -抱歉  琳达
- existing 2016 reelection funds... - Excuse me. Linda.
彼得・罗素死了
Peter Russo is dead.
自杀
Suicide.
他被发现死在车库里  汽车没熄火
He was found in his garage with the car still running.
我很遗憾  弗兰克
I'm so sorry, Frank.
-我能出去一会儿吗  先生  -当然
- May I have a moment, sir? - Of course.
我再去搜集些信息  草拟一份声明
I will get more information and start drafting a statement.
重新做安排  弗兰克方便的时候再谈
Let's reschedule. Whenever is best for Frank.
弗兰西斯  彼得今早被发现死在车库里  汽车没有熄火
国会议员彼得・罗素
Congressman Peter Russo was found dead
今早被发现死在
early this morning in the parking garage...
我们怎么没报道这个
why didn't we break this?
他华盛顿公寓楼下的车库里
of his apartment building in Washington D.C.
据报称罗素从周六起便不见踪影
U.S. Secret Service Agents discovered his body after reports
美国特勤处特工发现了他的尸体
that Russo had been missing since Saturday.
该死
Fuck!
他的尸体被运往华盛顿法医办公室
His body was transferred to the D.C. Coroner's office
进行验尸并确定是否为自杀身亡
where an autopsy is expected to confirm his death as a suicide.
罗素是来自费城的资浅议员
A junior congressman from Philadelphia...
今年36岁
Russo was 36 years old
佐伊
Zoe.
快看
Look at this.
育有两个孩子
And is survived by two children.
我得去办公室了
I gotta get to the office.
罗素本在竞选宾州州长
Russo was in the midst of a heated battle
竞选十分激烈
for the governorship of Pennsylvania.
他最后一次公开发言是在匹兹堡WZPZ电台
He was last heard publicly during a morning political radio show
一档早间政治节目中
on Pittsburgh station WZPZ.
在采访过程中
Now, during the interview,
他言词不清
he slurred his words,
头脑混乱  让很多人认为
he sounded disoriented leading many to believe
克里斯蒂娜
Christina.
他旧瘾复发
that he had relapsed...
能帮我订一张去特区的火车票吗
Can you get me a train back to D.C.?
本台将继续播报
Right here on this TV station for all
关于彼得・罗素议员自杀
the late-breaking details about this major news story:
这条重大新闻的最新详细情况
the suicide of congressman Peter Russo.
这就回家
我简直无法表达
I find it very difficult to
此刻心里的感受
express everything that I'm feeling right now,
我知道克莱尔也是这样
and I know Claire feels exactly the same.
彼得对我们来说很特别
Peter was very special to us.
他具有一种磁力
A sort of magnetic presence
使他接触的每个人都为之振奋
that electrified everyone he touched.
过去几个月里  我和我丈夫与他的友谊日渐深厚
My husband and I became very close to him in the past several month.
彼得不只是一位同僚  不只是我们的朋友
Peter was more than a college, more than a friend.
更亲如家人
He was family.
我们对他的孩子和母亲深表同情
Our hearts go out to his children and his mother.
也向所有了解他
To all of those who knew him
曾与他共事和爱他的人表达慰问
and worked with him and loved him.
我们希望各位能尊重他们的隐私
We would ask that all of you respect their privacy,
对他们的伤痛给予尊重
and honor their lost.
今天对于美国国会  对于宾州人民
Today is indeed a sad day for the United States' Congress,
对于我们所有人
for the state of Pennsylvania,
都是沉痛的一天
and for all of us.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
■
美国大选是在11月第一个星期二  这是美国初建国时就定下来的
选在11月  是因为大量选民是在远郊的农民
他们入秋收了庄稼后才有时间投票
同时因为美国有着浓厚的基督教传统
所以周末大家都要去教堂  然后周一启程去投票
地广人稀  农民们骑驴赶马  往往要走上一天才能到投票站
于是投票日被定在星期二
翻译  ~某人
翻译  噎死青春
翻译  小蟹
翻译  waterlike
翻译  sakura
翻译  风吹日落
翻译  某豚
翻译  猪猪
翻译  小饭
时间轴  Poxle
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
校对   草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第十一集
人人影视倾情奉献